Once Again Lord God me it's Jeff the
same Kid that used to Cry on his kne his
would his Pop already G so you prom to
be me But I feel like you forgot to
be I'm Hur and I know that more prom to
me But honestly I can't pict me
obviously for my eyes to see but
thinking me from thinking posi as I take
my life persal my times my fears the
Tears i c to my Take GR I'm here
myp se it on the and thought  happen to
me then i never That it happ hold back
tear as i Pass
by only Who Got
blci slow for meck like a on me spin
like slow it for me This Ain't show but
you view baby girl ST Fly like a Beauty
your boy Back to another Day another
dollar at you but Before I bounce One
last request move like a Snake for me
baby No contest I love the Way You move
I love the Way You I Love Your attitude I
won't forget the Way You walk I'm
feeling you you this girl you
Feeling me  let do this girl Uh I love
the Way You move I  love the Way You talk
I Love Your attitude I won't forget the
Way You walk Feeling you you this girl
you know you feel
me you whenever you call me
You Don't Have To worry alls you got All
my love I will be there for you whenever
you Call Me
Baby I know what you need leave It To Me
Bo
[Music]
Happy girl Take home
up and All f some li off the lip with
and SP old taking
back play The Game i Tell you how it
Feel the ones playing games the  ones to
Keep it real Chick try toim now I got so
I can't be like stepping on ban but for
times I be e ind
Got out Send around to
myy
had I was said
i
and signs up and Walking but I'm a
product of garbage my mom was a reab to
bead un andin Bl had Kid Who that How
They not be b
got that For You When me You don't have to
wor all you got All my love I will be
there for you whenever you Call Me
Baby I know what you need leave It To Me
boy you'll be happy For You Always  Just
call me whenever you Call on me I will
be right there I'm so there For You Just
Call on me my love
[Music]
will
an